Guide to the Mathew B. Brady and Levin Corbin Handy Photographic Studios Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Collected Photographs and Artifacts, circa 1840-circa 1940; Series IV; (23 boxes)
  - John J. Jarvis Photographs, (122 photographic prints)
    - Stereographs by John F. Jarvis and Sold by Underwood & Underwood on Tan Boards, (47 photographic prints)
      - Virginia, Arlington National Cemetery
        - Girls sitting among graves and a man standing, near the grave of Charles E. Shaw, Private, Maine Heavy Artillery, Site 6709 (Box 56, Folder 2720)
        - Monument to Philip Henry Sheridan (Box 56, Folder 2721-2722)
      - Virginia, Fort Monroe. Soldiers eating before transporting to Cuba, 1898 (Box 56, Folder 2723)
      - Virginia, Mount Vernon. Family dining room (Box 56, Folder 2724)
      - Virginia, Newport News
        - Barges loaded with troops en route to Puerto Rico (Box 56, Folder 2725)
        - General Grant's Brigade en route to Puerto Rico (Box 56, Folder 2726)
      - Unidentified locations
        - Battleship, (2 photographic prints) (Box 56, Folder 2727)
        - Crowd of people along a waterway (Box 56, Folder 2728)
        - Detail from a cyclorama of the Battle of Gettysburg, shows a field hospital and headquarters of George Gordon Meade at the Battle of Gettysburg, 1864, painted by Paul Philippoteaux (Box 56, Folder 2729)
        - Mannequin in a kitchen display, (2 photographic prints) (Box 56, Folder 2730)
        - Residence (Box 56, Folder 2731)
        - Sailors ferrying civilians, (2 photographic prints) (Box 56, Folder 2732)
        - Sailors posed on a battleship by a sculptural figure, circa 1885 (Box 56, Folder 2733)
        - Spinning wheel and fireplace (Box 56, Folder 2734)
        - Still Life. Japanese golden rayed lily (Lilium auratum) (Box 56, Folder 2735)
    - Boudoir Cards of Washington, District of Columbia, and Vicinity, (40 photographic prints)
      Photographic prints created and published by John F. Jarvis of buildings and location in the city and vicinity of Washington, District of Columbia, as well as the Arlington National Cemetery in Arlington, Virginia, and Mount Vernon, located near Alexandria, Virginia.
      Arranged alphabetically by geographical location, therein alphabetically by structure, and followed by details of statues in Washignton, District of Columbia.
      - District of Columbia, Washington
        - Anderson Cottage (Box 57, Folder 2736)
        - Corcoran Gallery of Art (Box 57, Folder 2737)
        - Lincoln Park. "[Abraham] Lincoln Freeing the Slaves" by Thomas Bell (Box 57, Folder 2738)
        - McPherson Square. Brigadier General James B McPherson Statue sculpted by Louis T. Rebisso (Box 57, Folder 2739)
        - Peace Monument, (2 photographic prints) (Box 57, Folder 2740)
          Designed and sculpted by Franklin Simmons
        - Smithsonian Institution Building (Box 57, Folder 2741-2742)
        - State, War, and Navy Department Building (Box 57, Folder 2743)
        - Thomas Circle and Luther Place Memorial Church, and statue of Major General George H. Thomas (Box 57, Folder 2744)
        - Thomas Circle and Portland Flats apartment building (Box 57, Folder 2745)
        - United States Capitol Building
          - Exteriors (Box 57, Folder 2746-2748)
            2 photographic prints of the eastern front of the building
          - Interiors (Box 57, Folder 2749-2750)
        - National Statuary Hall
          - Ethan Allen sculpted by Larkin G. Mead (Box 57, Folder 2751)
          - Robert Fulton by Howard Roberts (Box 57, Folder 2752)
        - United States National Museum (Box 57, Folder 2753)
          Later the Smithsonian Institution, Arts and Industries Building
        - United States Patent Office Building (Box 57, Folder 2754)
        - United States Pension Bureau (Box 57, Folder 2755)
        - United States Soldiers' Home, (2 photographic prints) (Box 57, Folder 2756)
        - Washington Monument (Box 57, Folder 2757)
        - White House
          - Exteriors (Box 57, Folder 2758-2759)
          - Interiors (Box 57, Folder 2760-2761)
        - Winfield Circle. Major General Winfield Scott sculpted by Henry Kirke Brown (Box 57, Folder 2762)
      - Virginia, Arlington National Cemetery
        - Arlington House, (2 photographic prints) (Box 57, Folder 2763)
        - Section 13, Sites 6405-6408, (2 photographic prints) (Box 57, Folder 2764)
      - Virginia, Mount Vernon
        - Residence, (2 photographic prints) (Box 57, Folder 2765)
        - Tomb of George Washington, (2 photographic prints) (Box 57, Folder 2766)
  - Underwood & Underwood Stereographs, (138 photographic prints)
    Underwood & Underwood was an early producer and distributor of stereoscopic and other photographic images, and became a pioneer in the field of news-bureau photography. It was founded in 1882 in Ottawa, Kansas by brothers, Elmer Underwood (1859-1947) and Bert Underwood (1862-1943). They moved their operations to Baltimore, Maryland, and to New York, New York, in 1891. In 1920, the company sold most of its catalog of stereographs to the Keystone View Company.
    - Stereographs of the Holy Land, With Numbers, (58 photographic prints)
      Stereographs under the heading are arranged by numbers on the cards.
      - 2. The Bazaar of Jaffa on a market day, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2767)
      - 3. A Caravan Of Camels In The Narrow Road Approaching Jaffa, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2768)
      - 4. Plowing in the fertile Plain of Sharon, Lydda, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2769)
      - 5. Pass of Upper Bethhoron from the South. Scene of Hebrew victories; Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2770)
      - 7. Jerusalem from Mt. Scopus at the northeast, showing nearly the whole city (Box 58, Folder 2771)
      - 8. Damascus Gate in North wall; South past Church of Holy Sepulchre, Jerusalem (Box 58, Folder 2772)
      - 9. The Jaffa Gate, from outside, Jerusalem (Box 58, Folder 2773)
      - 10. Jerusalem on the west, view south from new tower over the walls (Box 58, Folder 2774)
      - 11. The Valley of Kedron and Village of Siloam, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2775)
      - 15. "Unclean! Unclean!" Wretched lepers outside Jerusalem (Box 58, Folder 2776)
      - 20. Pilgrims in the Temple area; north from El Aksa to Dome of Rock, Jerusalem (Box 58, Folder 2777)
      - 21. The Jews' wailing place, outer wall of Solomon's Temple, Jerusalem (Box 58, Folder 2778)
      - 22. Inside a Jewish synagogue, showing Holy place and reader's platform, Jerusalem (Box 58, Folder 2779)
      - 23. Crowded bazaar and thoroughfare of David Street, view east to Olivet, Jerusalem (Box 58, Folder 2780)
      - 25. Church of the Holy Sepulchre, Jerusalem (Box 58, Folder 2781)
      - 27. Easter procession of greek Patriarch, entering Church of the Holy Sepulchre, Jerusalem (Box 58, Folder 2782)
      - 28. "The New Calvary", Outside the Damascus Gate, from the Northern Wall (Box 58, Folder 2783)
      - 30. Jerusalem and the Mount of Olives -- east from the Latin Hospice -- Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2784)
      - 33. Bethany where our Lord was anointed by Mary -- looking south from eastern slope of Olivet -- Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2785)
      - 35. Bethlehem of Judea, the birthplace of Jesus, west form the Church of the Nativity, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2786)
      - 36. Church of the Nativity, built where Jesus was born, Bethlehem of Judea (Box 58, Folder 2787)
      - 37. Barley harvest near Bethlehem (Box 58, Folder 2788)
      - 39. Hebron, the Home of Abraham, Issac and Jacob -- from the east -- Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2789)
      - 40. Mosque Machpelah, the Burial Place of Abraham, Isaac and Jacob, Hebron, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2790)
      - 41. Gaza, lowland stronghold of the Philistines, from southeast, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2791)
      - 42. Scene of Goliath's defeat, valley of Elah, northwest, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2792)
      - 43. Sheikh El Raschid and his escorts, famous bedouins of Palestine, Bethpage (Box 58, Folder 2793)
      - 44. Marvelous gorge of brook Cherith and Elijah Convent, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2794)
      - 45. Plain of the Jordan, southeast from the ruins of ancient Jericho (Box 58, Folder 2795)
      - 46. Ruins of Jericho, showing building (left) and city wall (right), Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2796)
      - 47. Baptizing in the Jordan, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2797)
      - 49. Mount Nebo, south from Wady Ayun Musa, showing road to Jordan, Syria (Box 58, Folder 2798)
      - 51. Old road from Jericho to Ai, west among hills of Benjamin, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2799)
      - 52. From Ramah, traditional home of Samuel, northeast toward Gilead, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2800)
      - 54. Women grinding at the mill (Box 58, Folder 2801)
      - 55. Bread making in the court of a Syrian home, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2802)
      - 56. Gathering tares from wheat in the stony fields of Bethel, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2803)
      - 57. Shiloh, scene of old religious assemblies, from the southeast, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2804)
      - 60. A Samaritan woman at Jacob's Well (Box 58, Folder 2805)
      - 61. Passover, as celebrated today by the Samaritans, Mount Gerisim, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2806)
      - 62. Shechem, an early centre of Hebrew history, looking southwest from Mount Ebal (Box 58, Folder 2807)
      - 64. Samaria, once proud and beautiful center of northern Kingdom, seen from southern Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2808)
      - 70. The mound of Megiddo from the southeast Samaria, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2809)
      - 71. Four thousand years unchanged, patriarchal life in Palestine today (Box 58, Folder 2810)
      - 72. North from Gilboa over Jezreel plain to Sea of Galilee, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2811)
      - 74. Broad sunny plain on Esdraelon and Mount Carmel west from mount Gilboa, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2812)
      - 75. From 'Little Hormon' northwest across Esdraelon Plain to Nazareth, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2813)
      - 77. Beautiful Nazareth; outlook south from hills above town to historic Esdraelon, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2814)
      - 78. Ancient 'Fountain of the Virgin', where Mary came for water, Nazareth, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2815)
      - 79. A threshing floor in the hills of Galilee, the women winnowing, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2816)
      - 83. The storied Sea of Galilee and its wall of hills; north over Tiberiason west bank, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2817)
      - 89. Traditional Capernaum, Christ's home by Galilee form the northwest, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2818)
      - 91. West over Sea of Galilee form above Karse (Gergesa) to Horns of Hattin, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2819)
      - 92. Plain of the Upper Jordan, north from near Lake Huleh to Mount Hermon, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2820)
      - 93. Down the upper Jordan Valley, southwest from Caesarea Philippi on Mount Hermon, Palestine (Box 58, Folder 2821)
      - 96. Ancient citadel in the sea at Sidon, Syria (Box 58, Folder 2822)
      - 97. The oldest of the Sacred Cedars of Lebanon, Monarch of the 400 (Box 58, Folder 2823)
      - 99. Damascus and its gardens form the northwest, Syria (Box 58, Folder 2824)
    - Stereographs on Tan Boards, (41 photographic prints)
      Stereographs under the heading are arranged alphabetically by location of the subject matter.
      - District of Columbia, Washington
        - Agricultural grounds, Smithsonian Institution, United States Capitol Building, and Library of Congress, from the Washington Monument, (2 photographic prints) (Box 59, Folder 2825)
        - President William McKinley and Admiral George Dewey on a reviewing stand, 1899 Oct 3; (2 photographic prints) (Box 59, Folder 2826)
        - President William McKinley and Admiral George Dewey on a reviewing stand, Benediction by Cardinal James Gibbons, 1899 Oct 3; (7 photographic prints) (Box 59, Folder 2827-2828)
        - President William McKinley and Admiral George Dewey on a reviewing stand, Opening Prayer by Dr. Butler, 1899 Oct 3 (Box 59, Folder 2829)
        - United States Botanic Garden Building. Interior (Box 59, Folder 2830)
        - United States Capitol Building, (2 photographic prints) (Box 59, Folder 2831)
        - United States Capitol Building. Interior. House of Representatives Chamber. Secretary of State John Milton Hay delivering a eulogy to William McKinley, 1901 Sep 17 (Box 59, Folder 2832)
        - White House and the United States Treasury Building from the Navy Department, 1902 (Box 59, Folder 2833)
        - White House and the United States Treasury Building from the Navy Department, 1902; (3 photographic prints) (Box 59, Folder 2834)
        - White House. Exterior. South front (Box 59, Folder 2835)
        - White House. Interior. East Room, Crescent table with settings and flowers awaiting guests for a dinner for Prince Henry, (2 photographic prints) (Box 59, Folder 2836)
        - White House. Interior. East Room, Roses on mantel (Box 59, Folder 2837)
      - England, London. Parade celebrating the Jubilee of Queen Victoria (Box 59, Folder 2838-2839)
      - Louisiana, New Orleans. Lower Levee Sugar Landing (Box 59, Folder 2840)
      - Russia, Kiev. Alexandrofski Slope and Dnieper River (Box 59, Folder 2841)
      - South Africa, Pretoria. Informal portrait of Frederick Sleigh Roberts, 1st Earl Roberts (Box 59, Folder 2842)
      - Unidentified locations
        - Caught napping, group of pigs sleeping (Box 59, Folder 2843)
        - Family composed of a man, woman, and boy posed standing by a wooden tipi (Box 59, Folder 2844)
        - Live oaks, fringed with Spanish moss, (2 photographic prints) (Box 59, Folder 2845)
        - Man and woman walking on a road near a tall rock face (Box 59, Folder 2846)
        - Marketplace from above (Box 59, Folder 2847)
        - Military parade, (3 photographic prints) (Box 59, Folder 2848-2849)
        - Small castle on rocky land from the water (Box 59, Folder 2850)
        - Two men standing in a rocky landscape (Box 59, Folder 2851)
        - Urban location with an equestrian statue (Box 59, Folder 2852)
    - Stereographs on Gray Boards, (39 photographic prints)
      - District of Columbia, Washington
        - Informal portrait of Edith Kermit Carow Roosevelt, 1903 (Box 60, Folder 2853)
        - Library of Congress. Thomas Jefferson Building. Great Hall (Box 60, Folder 2854)
        - Lincoln Park. Statue, Lincoln Freeing the Slaves, by Thomas Bell, (2 photographic prints) (Box 60, Folder 2855)
        - National Mall with the Washington Monument (Box 60, Folder 2856)
        - Pennsylvania Avenue (Box 60, Folder 2857)
        - Pennsylvania Avenue NW, toward the United States Capitol Building northeast from the United States Treasury Building, (2 photographic prints) (Box 60, Folder 2858)
        - Pennsylvania Avenue NW, toward the White House from the United States Capitol Building, (2 photographic prints) (Box 60, Folder 2859)
        - State, War, and Navy Department Building. Interior. Diplomatic Room, circa 1903 (Box 60, Folder 2860)
        - Thomas Circle and Luther Place Memorial Church, statue of George H. Thomas (Box 60, Folder 2861)
        - United States Capitol Building, interiors
          - House of Representatives Chamber. Secretary of State John Milton Hay delivering a eulogy to William McKinley, 1901 Sep 17; (2 photographic prints) (Box 60, Folder 2862)
          - Old Supreme Court Chamber (Box 60, Folder 2863)
        - United States Pension Building. Interior. Decorated for an inaugural ball (Box 60, Folder 2864)
        - United States Treasury Building. Funeral procession of William McKinley, 1901 Sep 17 (Box 60, Folder 2865)
        - White House, exterior. South front (Box 60, Folder 2866)
        - White House, interiors
          - Blue Room (Box 60, Folder 2867)
          - East Room, circa 1901 (Box 60, Folder 2868)
      - England
        - Langdale. Dungeon Gill waterfall and natural bridge (Box 60, Folder 2869)
        - London. Oxford Street, 1895 (Box 60, Folder 2870)
        - Rydal Village. Rydal Mount and Gardens, home of William Wordsworth (Box 60, Folder 2871)
      - Illinois. Chicago. Great Union Stockyards (Box 60, Folder 2872)
      - Ohio. Dayton. Soldier's Home, interior. Men eating, 1902; (6 photographic prints) (Box 60, Folder 2873)
      - Pennsylvania. Pittsburgh. 5th Avenue West from Smithfield, 1902 (Box 60, Folder 2874)
      - Virginia, Arlington National Cemetery. Girls and woman near a urn with the Arlington House in the distance, (2 photographic prints) (Box 60, Folder 2875)
      - Virginia, Arlington National Cemetery. Girls sitting among graves and a man standing, near the grave of Charles E. Shaw, Private, Maine Heavy Artillery, Site 6709 (Box 60, Folder 2876)
      - Virginia, Fort Monroe. Individuals posed sitting on cannon in brestworks, 1893 (Box 60, Folder 2877)
      - Unidentified locations
        - Body of water with a small island in it and mountains in the distance (Box 60, Folder 2878)
        - Cathedral on a street corner (Box 60, Folder 2879)
        - Children and adult posed by an arched bridge or aqueduct (Box 60, Folder 2880)
        - House in a distance from a stone and iron fence (Box 60, Folder 2881)
  - Album of Mary Westerman, (20 photographic prints)
    Album compiled by Mary Westerman, who may have been a member of the extended Handy family or an acquaintance.
    The photographic prints have been removed from the original album and arranged in the original order of the album, and are followed by the album
    - Carte-de-visite of an infant (Box 61, Folder 2882)
      Photograph by Isaac S. Bradley of Dayton, Ohio
    - Tintype of an infant (Box 61, Folder 2883)
    - Carte-de-visite of a woman (Box 61, Folder 2884)
    - Tintype of a young child with woman partially out of the frame (Box 61, Folder 2885)
    - Tintype of a young boy (Box 61, Folder 2886)
    - Tintype of an infant held by a woman draped in a blanket (Box 61, Folder 2887)
    - Tintype of a woman (Box 61, Folder 2888)
    - Carte-de-visite of a man (Box 61, Folder 2889)
    - Carte-de-visite of a man in uniform (Box 61, Folder 2890)
      Photograph by Louis Seebohm of Dayton, Ohio
    - Carte-de-visite of a boy and girl (Box 61, Folder 2891)
    - Carte-de-visite of a woman (Box 61, Folder 2892)
    - Tintype of a girl (Box 61, Folder 2893)
    - Carte-de-visite of Alexander III of Russia (Box 61, Folder 2894)
      Photograph by James Russell and Sons, Chichester, England
    - Tintype of a woman (Box 61, Folder 2895)
    - Carte-de-visite of a woman identified as Lib Angel (Box 61, Folder 2896)
    - Tintype of a man (Box 61, Folder 2897)
    - Carte-de-visite of a woman identified as Mary Westerman (Box 61, Folder 2898)
    - Tintype of a woman (Box 61, Folder 2899)
    - Tintype of a woman (Box 61, Folder 2900)
    - Carte-de-visite of a man identified as Tom Westerman (Box 61, Folder 2901)
    - Album (Box 61, Folder 2902)
  - Other Photographs, (313 photographs)
    This subseries includes photographs by a variety of photographers with different presentation methods.
    This subseries is arranged by cased photographs, tintypes, carte-de-viste albums and cartes-de-visite, stereograph cards, cabinet photographs, bourdior cards, and various sizes of prints,
    - Cased Photographs, (31 items)
      Cased photographs arranged by format -- daguerreotypes, ambrotypes, and other wet collodion processes, therein ascending by size -- and then by components -- cases and mats, therein ascending by size.
      - Daguerreotypes, 14 daguerreotypes, ranging in size from eitheenth plate to quarter plate (Box 62, Folder 2903-2915)
        Daguerreotypes of children, women, and men by primarily unidentified photographers.
        Single examples exist from the studios of Julien Vannerson of Washington, D.C., and Perkins of Baltimore, Maryland
      - Daguerreotype of a man, identified as Alphonse Marie Louise Prat de Lamartine, 1 daguerreotype, half plate, in a glass frame (Box 62, Folder 2916)
        Alphonse Marie Louise Prat de Lamartine (1790-1869) was a French writer, poet and politician
      - Ambrotypes, 8 ambrotypes, ranging in size from sixth pate to quarter plate (Box 62, Folder 2917-2924)
        Ambrotypes of children, women, men, and a dog by primarily unidentified photographers
      - Tintype of a man, ninth plate, in a full case, 1 tintype, ninth plate, in a full case (Box 62, Folder 2925)
      - Wet collodion process on porcelain of a woman, 1 wet collodion process on porcelain, quarter plate, hand colored, not in a case (Box 62, Folder 2926)
      - Case components for cased photographs, (3 case components) (Box 62, Folder 2927-2929)
        Includes case bottoms, as well as a full quarter plate case with an inscription, "J. P. Adams, 1846"
      - Mats, 4 mats, ranging in size from twelfth plate to three-quarter plate (Box 62, Folder 2930-2936)
        Mats for cased photographs, including examples from the studio of Jesse Harrison Whitehurst of Lynchburg or Richmond, Virginia, and Thomas Faris of Cincinnati, Ohio.
    - Tintypes, (41 tintype photographs)
      Tintypes of identified individuals, as well as unidentified children, women, men, and groups by primarily unidentified photographers
      Arranged alphbetically by the surname of the subject followed by unidentified subjects.
      - Bailey, William (Mrs.) (Box 63, Folder 2937)
      - Bright, Julia (Box 63, Folder 2938)
      - Demms, George (Box 63, Folder 2939)
      - Gessford, George (Box 63, Folder 2940)
      - Handy, John Bright, circa 1890 (Box 63, Folder 2941)
        Taken in Atlantic City, New Jersey
      - Hudsons, H. (Box 63, Folder 2942)
      - Johnston, Arvine, posed standing with an unidentified man posed sitting (Box 63, Folder 2943)
      - Lincoln, Abraham (Box 63, Folder 2944)
      - Little, S. M. (Box 63, Folder 2945)
      - Longstreet, M. J. (Mrs.) (Box 63, Folder 2946)
      - Middleton, Benjamin, posed standing with an unidentified man posed sitting (Box 63, Folder 2947)
      - Olden, Nellie Wise (Box 63, Folder 2948)
      - Yates, Katie (Box 63, Folder 2949)
      - Zimmerman, John R., posed sitting with an unidentified man posed standing (Box 63, Folder 2950)
      - Zimmerman, John R., with his grandson, Robert Zimmerman Bassett, circa 1883 (Box 63, Folder 2951)
      - Three women, identified from left to right, Mrs. Wood, Mary M. Zimmerman, and Clara Kimball (Box 63, Folder 2952)
      - Unidentified children, (4 tintype photographs) (Box 63, Folder 2953)
      - Unidentified men, (10 tintype photographs) (Box 63, Folder 2954)
        Includes a tintype by the Whitehurst Gallery, Washington, District of Columbia
      - Unidentified women, (8 tintype photographs) (Box 63, Folder 2955)
      - Unidentified man and woman (Box 63, Folder 2956)
      - Groups of unidentified men, (2 tintype photographs) (Box 63, Folder 2957)
    - Cartes-de-visite, (64 photographic prints)
      Cartes-de-visite portraits of identified and unidentified individuals.
      Arranged alphabetically by the surname or corporate name of the photographer, and therein by the surname of the subject
      - Anthony, Edward, and Henry T. Anthony
        Studio in New York, New York
        - Longstreet, James (Box 64, Folder 2958)
        - Pike, Albert (Box 64, Folder 2959)
        - Copy photograph of a composite, "Our Peace Commissioners for 1865," David Glasgow Farragut, Ulysses S. Grant, Abraham Lincoln, David Dixon Porter, Philip Henry Sheridan, William Tecumseh Sherman, George Henry Thomas (Box 64, Folder 2960)
      - Averill, Henry K., Jr.
        Studio in Plattsburgh, New York
        - Boy and girl (Box 64, Folder 2961)
      - Baird, Archibald H.
        Studio in Middletown, New York
        - Price, Daisy (Box 64, Folder 2962)